Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
  - Area M - Wales and Monmouthshire, Nov 1948-Mar 1950
    - Glamorgan, Pontypridd, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/533; 1.0 file
    - Merioneth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/534; 1.0 file
    - Newport, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/535; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Abertillery, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/536; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Bedwellty, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/537; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Ebbw Vale, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/538; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Monmouth, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/539; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/540; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/541; 1.0 file
    - Pembroke, Nov 1948-Mar 1950; CCO 1/7/542; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8
  - Area A - London, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/1-CCO 1/8/43
    - Battersea North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/1; 1.0 file
    - Battersea South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/2; 1.0 file
    - Bermondsey, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/3; 1.0 file
    - Bethnal Green, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/4; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/5; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/6; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/7; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/8/1; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/8/2; 1.0 file
    - City of Westminster, Abbey, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/8/3; 1.0 file
    - City of Westminster, St. George's, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/8/4; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/9; 1.0 file
    - Fulham East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/10; 1.0 file
    - Fulham West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/11; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich (1), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/12/1; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich (2), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/12/2; 1.0 file
    - Hackney South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/13; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/14; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/15/1; 1.0 file
    - Hampstead, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/16; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South (1), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/17/1; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South (2), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/17/2; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/18; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/19; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/20; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/21; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/22; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Brixton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/23; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Norwood, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/24; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Vauxhall, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/25; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/26; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/27; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/28; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/29; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/30; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/31; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/32; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/33/1; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/34/1; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/35; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/36; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/37; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/38; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Clapham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/39; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Putney, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/40; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Streatham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/41; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/42/1; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East - By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/42/2; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East - By-Election, Organisation Department file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/42/3; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/43/1; 1.0 file
    - University of London, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/43/2; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/44-CCO 1/8/77
    - Carlisle, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/44
    - Cumbria, Penrith, and the Border Division, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/45; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven Division, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/46; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/47; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/48; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/49/50; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/49; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/50; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/51; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/52; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/53/54; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/53; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/54; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/55; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Aukland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/56; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/57; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/58; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/59; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/60; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/61; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/62; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Jarrow, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/63; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West Durham Division, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/64; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/65; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/66/67; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/66; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/67; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/68; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/69; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/70; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North (1), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/71/1; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North (2), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/71/2; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/72; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/73; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/74; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/75; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/76; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/77; 1.0 file
  - Area C - NorthWest, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/78-CCO 1/8/157
    - Altrincham and Sale, Apr 1950-Aug 1951 Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/78; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/79; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/80; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/81/82; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/81; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/82; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/83; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/84; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/85; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/86; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/87; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/88; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/89; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/90; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/91; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/92; 1.0 file
    - Accrington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/93; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-Under-Lyne, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/94; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in Furness, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/95; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/96/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/96; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/98/99; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/98; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/99; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/100/101; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/100; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/101; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/102; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/103; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/104; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/105; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/106/1; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden - By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/106/2; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden - By-Election, G.D.'s file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/106/3; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/107; 1.0 file
    - Leigh, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/108; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/109/117; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Edgehill, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/109; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Exchange, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/110; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Garston, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/111; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Kirkdale, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/112; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Scotland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/113; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Toxteth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/114; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Walton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/115; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Wavertree, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/116; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/117; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/118/126; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Ardwick, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/118; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Blackley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/119; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Cheetham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/120; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Clayton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/121; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Exchange, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/122; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Gorton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/123; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/124/1; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/124/2; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Withington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/125; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Wythenshawe, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/126; 1.0 file
    - Nelson and Colne, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/127; 1.0 file
    - Oldham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/128/129; 1.0 file
    - Oldham East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/128; 1.0 file
    - Oldham West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/129; 1.0 file
    - Preston, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/130/131; 1.0 file
    - Preston North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/130; 1.0 file
    - Preston South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/131; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/132; 1.0 file
    - Rossendale, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/133; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/134; 1.0 file
    - Salford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/135/136; 1.0 file
    - Salford East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/135; 1.0 file
    - Salford West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/136; 1.0 file
    - Southport, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/137; 1.0 file
    - Stretford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/138; 1.0 file
    - Warrington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/139; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/140; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Chorley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/141; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Clithero, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/142; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Darwen, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/143; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/144; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/145; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Huyton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/146; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ince, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/147; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Lancaster, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/148; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Middleton and Prestwich, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/149; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/150; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Newton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/151; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, North Fylde, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/152; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/153/1; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk - By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/153/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk - By-Election, Organisation Department file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/153/3; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk - By-Election, G.D.'s file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/153/4; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, South Fylde, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/154; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/155/1; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton - By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/155/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton - By-Election, Organisation Department file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/155/3; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton - By-Election, G.D.'s file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/155/4; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Widnes, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/156; 1.0 file
    - Westmorland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/157; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/158-CCO 1/8/213
    - Barnsley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/158/1
    - Mid Yorkshire Federation, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/158/2; 1.0 file
    - Combined English Universities Conservative Associations, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/158/3; 1.0 file
    - Bately and Morley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/159; 1.0 file
    - Bradford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/160/163; 1.0 file
    - Bradford Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/160; 1.0 file
    - Bradford East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/161; 1.0 file
    - Bradford North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/162; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/163; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/164/1; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough - By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/164/2; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough - By-Election, Organisation Department file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/164/3; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough - By-Election, Mr Garmonsway's file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/164/4; 1.0 file
    - Dewsbury, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/165; 1.0 file
    - Doncaster, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/166; 1.0 file
    - Halifax, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/167; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/168/169; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/168; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/169; 1.0 file
    - Keighley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/170; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/171/174; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/171; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/172; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/173; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/174; 1.0 file
    - Leeds, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/175/181; 1.0 file
    - Leeds Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/175; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/176; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/177; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/178; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/179; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/180; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/181/1; 1.0 file
    - Pontefract, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/182; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/183; 1.0 file
    - Rotherham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/184; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/185/191; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Attercliffe, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/185; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Brightside, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/186; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hallam, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/187; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Healey, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/188; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hillsborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/189; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Neepsend, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/190/1; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Neepsend By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/190/2; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield Park, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/191; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/192; 1.0 file
    - York, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/193; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Barkston Ash, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/194; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Beverley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/195; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Bridlington, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/196; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/197; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Colne Valley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/198; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Dearne Valley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/199; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Don Valley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/200; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Goole, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/201; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/202; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Hemsworth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/203; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Normanton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/204; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Penistone, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/205; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Richmond, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/206; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rippon, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/207; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rother Valley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/208; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Scarborough and Whitby, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/209; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Shipley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/210; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Skipton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/211; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Sowerby, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/212; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Thirsk and Malton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/213; 1.0 file
  - Area E - East Midlands, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/214-CCO 1/8/255
    - Chesterfield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/214; 1.0 file
    - Derby, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/215/216; 1.0 file
    - Derby North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/215; 1.0 file
    - Derby South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/216; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Belper, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/217; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Bolsover, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/218; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, High Peak, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/219; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Ilkeston, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/220; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, North East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/221; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, South East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/222; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/223; 1.0 file
    - Leicester, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/224/227; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North East (A), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/224/1; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North East (B), Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/224/2; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North East By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/224/3; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North East By-Election Organisation Department file, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/224/4; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/225; 1.0 file
    - Leicester South East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/226; 1.0 file
    - Leicester South West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/227; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Bosworth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/228; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Harborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/229; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Loughborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/230; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Melton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/231; 1.0 file
    - Grimsby, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/232; 1.0 file
    - Lincoln, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/233; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Brig, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/234; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Gainsborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/235; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Grantham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/236; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Holland with Boston, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/237; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Horncastle, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/238; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Louth, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/239; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Rutland and Stamford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/240; 1.0 file
    - Northampton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/241; 1.0 file
    - Northants., Kettering, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/242; 1.0 file
    - Northants., Peterborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/243; 1.0 file
    - Northants., South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/244; 1.0 file
    - Northants., Wellingborough, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/245; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/246/249; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/246; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/247; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham North West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/248; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/249; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Bassetlaw, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/250; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Broxtowe, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/251; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Carlton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/252; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Mansfield, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/253; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Newark, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/254; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Rushcliffe, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/255; 1.0 file
  - Area F - West Midlands, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/256-CCO 1/8/313
    - Cheltenham, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/256; 1.0 file
    - Gloucester, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/257; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, Cirencester and Tewksbury, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/258; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/259; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, Stroud and Thornbury, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/260; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/261; 1.0 file
    - Herefordshire, Hereford, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/262; 1.0 file
    - Herefordshire, Leominster, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/263; 1.0 file
    - Shropshire, Ludlow, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/264; 1.0 file
    - Shropshire, Oswestry, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/265; 1.0 file
    - Shropshire, Shrewsbury, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/266; 1.0 file
    - Shropshire, The Wrekin, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/267; 1.0 file
    - Billston, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/268; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle under Lyme, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/269/1; 1.0 file
    - North Stafforshire Political Union, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/269/2; 1.0 file
    - Rowley Regis and Tipton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/270; 1.0 file
    - Smethwick, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/271; 1.0 file
    - Stoke-on-Trent, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/272/274; 1.0 file
    - Stoke-on-Trent Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/272; 1.0 file
    - Stoke-on-Trent North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/273; 1.0 file
    - Stoke-on-Trent South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/274; 1.0 file
    - Walsall, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/275; 1.0 file
    - Wednesbury, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/276; 1.0 file
    - West Bromwich, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/277; 1.0 file
    - Wolverhampton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/278/279; 1.0 file
    - Wolverhampton North East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/278; 1.0 file
    - Wolverhampton South West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/279; 1.0 file
    - Staffordshire, Brierley Hill, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/280; 1.0 file
    - Staffordshire, Burton, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/281; 1.0 file
    - Staffordshire, Cannock, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/282; 1.0 file
    - Staffordshire, Leek, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/283; 1.0 file